American Psychological Association Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellany, 1931-1986 (Box 719-725)
  - Veterans, education and job opportunities, 1946
NAESP National Association of Elementary School Principals
NAMH National Association for Mental Health
NASP National Association of School Psychologists
NEAR Newly Emerging Areas of Research
NIMH National Institute of Mental Health
NEPA National Environmental Policy Act
NISP National Information System for Psychology
NRC National Research Council
NRSTP National Register of Scientific and Technical Personnel
NSF National Science Foundation
OCMD Office of Communication Management and Development
OEO Office of Economic Opportunity
OVR Office of Vocational Rehabilitation (of Federal Security Agency)
P & the Law Division 41: Psychology and Law
P & E Division 34: Population and Environmental Psychology
PH Division 30: Psychological Hypnosis
PSIEP Project on Scientific Information Exchange in Psychology
PUPI Task Force on Psychologists' Use of Physical Interventions
SPSS Statistical Package for the Social Studies (computer program)
SPSSI Division 9: Society for the Psychological Study of Social Issues
SREB Southern Regional Education Board
SRSS Sociological Resources for the Social Sciences
TAMU Texas A & M University, College Station, Tex.
TFETMG Task Force on Employment Testing of Minority Groups
TORC Committee on Training in Rehabilitation Counseling
UAW United Automobile Workers
UNESCO United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization
VA Veterans Administration